Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Agency Files, 1947-2007
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1972-1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1986-1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1999 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Grievance (Local 107), 2001 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - National Board of the YMCA: Bargaining (Local 107), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel: Bargaining (Local 107), 1950-1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel: Bargaining (Local 107), 1972-1992 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Bargaining (Local 107), 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Bargaining (Local 107), 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Grievances/Personnel Issues (Local 107), 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Personnel (Local 107), 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - New Jersey Federation Agencies: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Arbitration, NLRB, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1975-1990 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 215), 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 215), 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Arbitration (Local 215), 2003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Retrenchment/Layoffs (Local 215), 2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative (Local 215), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-2003, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative (Local 215), 2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative--Comptroller NYC and NYS (Local 215), 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievances (Local 215), 1998-2003 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievances--Work Load (Local 215), 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievance--Rose Levy (Local 215), 1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievance--Irma Logas (Local 215), 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievance--Farshad Yeroshalmi (Local 215), 1993 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Conflict of Internet Policy (Local 215), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Health Benefits (Local 215), 1996-2000 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 215), 1994-2001, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Job Specialists (Local 215), 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Layoffs/Bumping/Retrenchment (Local 215), 2003 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Daniel O'Sullivan (Local 215), 1998-2001 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Sabbath Observance (Local 215), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Staff Directory (Local 215), 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Voluntary Retrenchment/Furlough (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - New York City--Administration for Children's Services: Bargaining, 1996-1999 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - New York City--Administration for Children's Services: Bargaining, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - New York City--Administration for Children's Services: Bargaining, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - New York City--Brooklyn Bureau of Community Services: Bargaining, 1991-1996 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - New York City--Brooklyn Bureau of Community Services: Bargaining, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - New York City--Brooklyn Bureau of Community Services: Bargaining, 1997-2002 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - New York Society for the Deaf: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-1999 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - New York State Association for Retarded Citizens: Bargaining (Local 253), 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1952-1963 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1965-1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1981-1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1998-2004 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1970, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153: Bargaining, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153: Bargaining, 1996-1999, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153: General Administrative, 1997-1999, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1990 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services: DC 1707 Staff Representive Files (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services: Grievance (Local 215), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Pomonok Home Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Pomonok Home Services: Grievances (Local 389), 1998-2000 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1956-1976 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1978-1981 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1993-1998 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1999-[2005] (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Quo Vadis Montessori Day Care Center: Grievances (Local 205), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Richard G. Rosenthal YM and YWHA of Northern Westchester: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Richard G. Rosenthal YM and YWHA of Northern Westchester: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Richard G. Rosenthal YM and YWHA of Northern Westchester: Personnel (Local 215), 1995-1998 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1956-1963 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1965-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), [1979]-1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1996-2000 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Grievances--Unfair Labor Practices Case (Local 215), 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Rockland ARC: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Samuel Field - Bay Terrace YM and YWHA: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Samuel Field - Bay Terrace YM and YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1995 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Samuel Field - Bay Terrace YM and YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-2000 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Selfhelp Community Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 1993-2001 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Selfhelp Community Services: General Administrative (Local 389), 1990-2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Services for the Aged: Grievances, General Administrative (Local 389), 1986-1989 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1951-1959 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1961-1971 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1973-1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1981-1986 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1985-1989 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1989-1992 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1993-2000 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Grievance (Local 215), 1995 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 1981-2003, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 1997-2002 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 1998-2002 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining--Management Proposals (Local 253), 1999-2003 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining--DC 1707 Contract Proposals (Local 253), 2001. undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining--Contract Amendment Votes (Local 253), 2000, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 2001-2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Audits, Clinics (Local 253), 1998-2001 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) (Local 253), 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--DC 1707 Health and Insurance Fund (Local 253), 2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Directions (Local 253), 2000-2001, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Dues (Local 253), 2001-2005 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Excessive Teacher Turnover Prevention Program (Local 253), 2001-2003 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Labor Management Committee (Local 253), 2002-2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Meetings (Local 253), 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disablilities (OMRDD) (Local 253), 2001, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Safety and Security (Local 253), 2005 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Union Demonstrations (Local 253), 2002 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 1996 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 2000-2004 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 2000-2005 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances, Class Action (Local 253), 2001-2003 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances/Personnel (Local 253), 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--Sharon David (Local 253), 1999-2005 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--Mary Leto (Local 253), 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--James McCarther (Local 253), 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--A-K (Local 253), 2000-2003 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--L-Mc (Local 253), 2000-2004 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--Me-Z (Local 253), 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Certification/Temporary Licenses (Local 253), 2001-2003 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Certification/Uncertified Teachers (Local 253), 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Employee Files (Local 253), 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Employee Handbook (Local 253), 1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 1988-2000 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 2002, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 253), 2003 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Layoffs and Transfers (Local 253), 2004 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Probationary Extensions (Local 253), 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Suspension/Termination Notices (Local 253), 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Various (Local 253), 2001 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievances (Local 215), 1988-2000 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Debra Burns (Local 215), 1997-1999 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Tatiana Plaxina (Local 215), 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Alla Ronin (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Grievance--Stella Weisberg (Local 215), 1997-1999 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Shorefront YM-YWHA of Brighton-Manhattan Beach: Personnel (Local 215), 1993-1999 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - St. Christopher's-Jennie Clarkson Child Care Services, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 215), 1997 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - St. Christopher's-Jennie Clarkson Child Care Services, Inc.: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - St. Mary's Children and Family Services: Reports, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - St. Mary's Children and Family Services (also Sisters of Mercy, Angel Guardian Children and Family Services): Unfair Labor Practices, NLRB Arbitration, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Susan E. Wagner Day Care Center: Grievances (Local 205), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Union Child Day Care Center, Inc.: Bargaining [Local 205], 1996 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations: Bargaining (Local 107), [1981]-1996 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1950-1955 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1956-1964 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1966-1970 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1972-1978 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1985-2005 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 107), 1996 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 107), 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Bargaining--Arbitration (Local 107), 1963-1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievances (Local 107), 1991-1999 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievances (Local 107), 1994-1999 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievances/Personnel (Local 107), 1997-2000 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievance--Victoria Brown (Local 107), 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Grievance--Ann Plutzer (Local 107), 1995-1998 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel (Local 107), 1995-1997 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1996-1998 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Hirings, Terminations, Resignations (Local 107), 1996-2000 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 107), 1972 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Reduction of Hours, Bargaining Unit Members (Local 107), 1995-2000 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - United Jewish Appeal (UJA)-Federation: Personnel--Retirement Plan (Local 107), 1962 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - United Jewish Appeal Communities (Council of Jewish Federations, United Jewish Appeal): DC 1707 Disenfranchisement, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - United States Home Care: General Administrative, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - United States Home Care: DC 1707 NLRB Case, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - United Synagogue of Conservative Judaism: Bargaining (Local 253), 1995 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - University Settlement: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Utopia Children's Center: Grievances, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Victims Information Bureau of Suffolk, Inc.: Bargaining, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - VNS Group Home Health Care: Bargaining, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Visiting Nurse Services (VNS): Grievance/Personnel, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - West Bronx Jewish Community Center: Bargaining, 1954-[1968] (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: Bargaining (Local 107), 1995-1998 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1994-1998 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: Grievances (Local 107), 1994-1999 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Women's American ORT/American ORT: Personnel (Local 107), 1994-1998 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Bargaining (Local 215), 1949-1959 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Bargaining (Local 215), 1960-1968 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Bargaining (Local 215), 1973-1975 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - YM and YWHA of Boro Park: Grievance (Local 215), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Reprentative Files (Local 215), 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: General Administrative (Local 215), 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1999 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - YM-YWHA of Mid-Westchester: Personnel (Local 215), 1993-1999 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Grievances (Local 215), 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Grievance--Veronica McKenzie (Local 215), 1993-1995 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-2000 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - YM and YWHA of Washington Heights and Inwood: Project Hope (Local 215), 1997 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - YM and YWHA Senior Housing Development Fund Corporation: Bargaining (Local 215), 1974-2006 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Zionist Organization of America: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Multiple Agencies: DC 1707 Staff Representative File (Locals 95/205), 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Multiple Agencies: Bargaining, Grievances (10 reels of 16 mm microfilm), 1950-1990 (Box 47)
- Series IV: Officers and Staff-Administrative Files, 1962-2004
  - Subseries IV:A: Local 1707, 1962-1965.
    One file, which includes mostly correspondence between Local 1707 officers (especially Benjamin Bially, Executive Director, 1963-1968) and AFSCME (including AFSCME President Jerry Wurf) over union procedural matters and organizing.
    - Correspondence, General Administrative, 1962-1965 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Subseries IV:B: Raglan George, Jr., 1973-2002.
    Raglan George, Jr. was elected Executive Director of 1707 in 2002. Previous roles within the Council included director of Local 95 (Head Start) and Local 205 (Day Care Employees). Material in this subseries (approximately three boxes of records) generally relates to the administration and concerns of these locals and predates George's tenure as Executive Director.
    - Administration for Children and Families (ACF), 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Agency for Child Development (ACD)--3% Cut, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Agenda for Children Tomorrow (ACT), 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Agenda for Children Tomorrow (ACT), 1994-1997 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Dues Reporting, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Pension, 1993-1995 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Child Care, 1997-1998, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Child Care Campaigns, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Child Care Reports, 1993-1997 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children, 2000, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - City Project, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Clippings/Press Releases, 1997, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), 1986-1997 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Committee on General Welfare Hearings, 1993-1997 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Conferences/Workshops, 1997, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Cornell Child Care Project, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 10)